Rick Miller Papers ARC.0054
Library and Archives
Rick Miller Papers
1970-1988
ARC.0054
Library and Archives
2.0 Linear feet 2 RC
The Rick Miller Papers span the years 1970-1988. The collection consists of documents collected by Miller while he was a production manager for the following artists: Aerosmith, Eric Carmen, Christopher Cross, ELO, Fleetwood Mac, The Jacksons, Ted Nugent, Lou Reed, The Rolling Stones, Santana, Bob Seger, Boz Scaggs, and Robin Trower. The papers document the featured tours rather than the artists and include riders, blueprints, stage plans, venue information, venue photographs, and lighting cues, as well as itineraries for artists and crew, correspondence, contracts, artist requests, and carnets (merchandise passports). The collection is arranged alphabetically by artist, and then chronologically by tour.
Biographical/Historical note
Rick Miller is a production manager, whose work in the 1970s and 1980s encompassed extensive concert touring.
Access Restrictions
Collection is open for research. Patrons must sign the Acknowledgment of Legal Responsibility and Privacy Rights form before using this collection. Please contact reference staff before visiting the library and Archives to use this collection.
Immediate Source of Acquisition note
The Rick Miller Papers were recieved by the Rock and Roll Hall of Fame and Museum, Inc. as a gift from Rick Miller on July 30, 1997.
Electric Light Orchestra.; Miller, Rick, tour producer.; Rolling Stones; Santana (Musical group); Scaggs, Boz, 1944-; Concert tours.
- Aerosmith, U.S. Tour, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  General note
  Contains venue photographs and layout.
- Carmen, Eric, Europe Tour, 1985 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Cross, Christopher, 1982-1983
  - Japan Tour, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Far East Tour, 1983 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- ELO, 1981-1987
  - U.K. Tour, 1981 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    Contains official program from tour.
  - U.S. Tour, 1981 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Europe Tour, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - U.S. Tour, 1987 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Fleetwood Mac, U.S. Tour, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  Contains photographs of venue and stage setup.
- The Jacksons, U.S. Tour, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Nugent, Ted, U.S. Tour, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  Contains venue and stage setup photographs.
- Reed, Lou, Australia Tour, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 12)
- The Rolling Stones, U.S. Tour, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 13)
- Santana, 1973-1976
  - Europe Tour, 1973 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Far East Tour, 1973 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - U.S. Tour, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Santana & Eric Clapton, U.S. Tour, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Australia Tour, 1976 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Far East Tour, 1976 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - U.S. Tour, 1976 (Box 2, Folder 3-4)
    Contains lighting cue book.
  - South American Tour, Undated (Box 2, Folder 5)
- Seger, Bob, U.S. Tour, 1978 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  Features venue and stage setup photographs.
- Scaggs, Boz, 1978-1988
  - Australia Tour, 1978 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - U.S. Tour, 1979 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Far East Tour, 1980 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - U.S. Tour, 1980 (Box 2, Folder 10-11)
  - Japan Tour, 1985 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Japan Tour, 1988 (Box 2, Folder 13)
- Toledo Jam, 1979 (Box 2, Folder 14)
- Trower, Robin, 1976-1977
  - U.S. Tour, 1976 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Far East Tour, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 16)
- Unidentified tour information, undated (Box 2, Folder 17)